// an array of objects containing question, choices, and indwex of answer
var quiz = [
    {
        question: 'If you type the following code in the console window, what result will you get?\n3 > 2 > 1 === false;',
        choices: ['true', 'false'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'JavaScript is a ___ -side programming language.',
        choices: ['Client', 'Server', 'Both', 'None'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following will write the message “Hello DataFlair!” in an alert box?',
        choices: ['alertBox(“Hello DataFlair!”);', 'alert(Hello DataFlair!);', 'msgAlert(“Hello DataFlair!”);', 'alert(“Hello DataFlair!”);'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'How do you find the minimum of x and y using JavaScript?',
        choices: ['min(x,y);', 'Math.min(x,y)', 'Math.min(xy)', 'min(xy);'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?',
        choices: ['while()', ' loop()', 'forEach()', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to upper case?',
        choices: ['toUpperCase()', 'toUpper()', 'changeCase(case)', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following function of Boolean object returns the primitive value of the Boolean object?',
        choices: ['toSource()', 'valueOf()', 'toString()', 'None of the above'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following function of String object executes the search for a match between a regular expression and a specified string?',
        choices: ['concat()', 'match()', 'replace()', 'search()'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following function of String object creates a string to be displayed as bold as if it were in a <b> tag?',
        choices: ['anchor()', 'big()', 'blink()', 'bold()'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following function of Array object returns the first (least) index of an element within the array equal to the specified value, or -1 if none is found?',
        choices: ['indexOf()', 'join()', 'lastIndexOf()', 'map()'],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following function of Array object returns true if at least one element in this array satisfies the provided testing function?',
        choices: ['reverse()', 'shift()', 'slice()', 'some()'],
        answer: 3
    }
];


